I'm feelin'
lucky, and getting a little target
practice in might do me a world of goods!
Got him!
That was too close.
If I hadn't returned to my normal
size, I'd be dead right now.
Luckily, time was on my side.
Your wimp-ass shrinking down to nothing
again was the best thing
to ever happen to me!
Damn, the bastard's still breathing!
damn it could that chatty dickhead have
pulled a one-two punch and weakened my
stand's power when he shrunk my body he's
on the move again come back little bummer
i want him to taste some major pain but
for now i gotta hide he's a loose cannon
if he finds me he'll do
whatever it takes to make
me squeal about the location
of the boss's daughter
It's so far, why's the
sidewalk so damn big?
Move it!
You're in my way, Dead tat!
Shit, this sucks!
What have we here?
It's been a fun ride. Chuckles.
You're a slippery one to say the least!
Once tiny feet break skin, you're doomed
to live out a life in a small small world.
Now let's have a little chat.
Bucciarati and crew.
Where are they hiding the boss's daughter?
Not with it.
Kill me, stronzo.
You might as well get
it over with already.
Just end it.
Because I actually value
the lives of my friends!
I would never screw them
over like that! Got it?
Narancia Girga, born a Leo in 1984.
At the age of 10...
Narancia...
Your mama beside you...
Mama...
Hey, Papa.
Mama had an eye sickness, right?
Piece of shit.
This dismal morning was the beginning of
what would become Narancia's new life.
I'll be right back.
Scusa, could you explain
something to me? Huh?
I was wondering, how many minutes do
you think it would take me to walk here?
Narancia had rebelled against his father.
He began to fraternize
with the wrong crowd,
refusing to come home and surviving
on whatever he stole that day.
Wow, it really worked!
I couldn't have done it
without your info, big bro!
I guess, but shouldn't you be in school?
You come from a decent family, right?
Hmph, like I care about them.
Only one thing matters in this world.
You're true friends. Yeah.
You know, you should dye
your hair blonde like mine.
You would look so damn cool. Huh?
I will!
Oh, shit! You did it!
Like the new hook?
Wow, what a tool!
Have you guys seen Big Bro?
Come to think of it, it's been a few days.
Then, the very next day...
Damn, you're stupid!
Get your grubby hands on the wall!
Stronsanto, your thieving
ass is going to jail me.
I didn't steal anything!
I wasn't...
Save your breath, kid.
A witness saw the whole thing.
What?
That's him!
That's the blonde Terra who robbed me!
What? You're wrong!
He's lying!
He bit me senseless and took all my money!
You better come clean, old bag!
I'm innocent and you know it!
I've had enough of your damn lies!
Just confess already! Hey!
I know we need answers, but
you have to let the boy go!
Oh, didn't you see that?
He was about to attack!
A robber.
She called me a blonde terror.
Could it be him?
No way. He'd never...
Don't even think that. Damn it!
Narancia was released one year later,
but in extremely poor health the officer
had injured his eye and the infection that
resulted was unrelenting when he returned
home his friends were
unusually standoffish
disgusting his mom died
from that eye disease
how did they know that
was a secret between big
bro and me wow so they
let you out already you
and that infected eye
should keep your distance
from now on it's true
big bro did it he was
caught so he blamed me
but the rumors surrounding
that horrible eye disease
scared no one more than
naranja himself this is
my destiny this disease
it's gonna kill me i'm gonna
die just like mama he had
no home no shoulder to cry
on and no hope to hold on
to he was 15 and awaiting
his inevitable death how sad
he's just a kid yes but we
should Keep our distance.
The young man led Narancia
into a local trattoria
and had a word for his friend
and the maitre d'. Hey!
This kid needs a plate
of spaghetti pronto!
You can handle it, right?
His friend asked not a single question,
and his face showed no sign of annoyance.
He simply placed the plate
of food he had ordered
for himself in front
of the disheveled boy.
He then made sure the boy
received proper medical treatment.
Three weeks later...
Why do this for me?
Why go to so much trouble?
I have no pretext.
You're welcome at my home,
though the choice lies with you.
I strongly suggest you go
back home to your parents.
You need to go to school. Got it?
Hey, uh, are you by chance a mafioso?
I don't want to go back to that life.
I want to work with you
and become a mafioso!
This isn't some game we're
playing, you eager shithead!
You ever spew that kind
of asinine crap again,
I'll give you the beating of your life!
Narancia took his words to heart and returned
home to resume his studies at school.
But he learned his lesson, and
would never trust his father again.
I wonder why that guy got so
serious with me all of a sudden.
It's not like I have
anything to work toward.
But his anger had no resentment or hatred.
Nothing about it came across
like it was meant to insult.
It was nothing like the way my
dad and those cops treated me.
Thinking back on it, it's like
his words filled me with courage.
I have to be a warrior.
That's the only way to join
up with someone like him.
Six months later,
Narancia made up his mind,
and met with the Cape Polpo
without Pucciarati's knowledge.
He passed the test and became a mafioso.
Narancia, if there ever was a time to
unburden yourself, that time would be now.
So tell me where the girl is.
That girl you want to abduct
isn't a mafioso or anything close!
She's just a freaking kid!
Bucciarati knows how to respect a command,
but not when it comes
to foul shit like this!
It's called human decency!
We gave our word we would protect her,
and that's exactly what we're gonna do!
Please, you should just give
up on the chivalry bullshit.
Why do I put up with this?
I'm not the least bit interested in that
heroic crap about friendship, loyalty,
and saving some girl.
At the moment,
all I care about is taking down the
good old boss and enjoying a drug group?
worth hundreds of billions.
You bastard!
Hmm.
We're talking hundreds of billions!
You really don't think a few heads
aren't gonna roll along the way?
That loot is ours for the taking!
We're not turning back now!
And if she's the boss's blood daughter,
then you better bet your
ass she's a stand user!
Of course, the boss wants to
keep that all under wraps.
We could just unmask him.
Her power is...
A BIGGEST CLUE TO HIS IDENTITY!
She's the key to taking
him down permanently! What?
You think that girl is a stand user?
Maybe you've heard.
Did you know South America is
home to the Southern Black Widow?
Its venom is particularly
lethal to humans.
This one, on the other
hand, is non-venomous.
I caught it in the sewer while
I was dodging your bullets.
He's completely harmless.
Though I shouldn't say harmless.
Since even the most benign spiders
deliver a bit of toxin with their nibble.
When it comes to paralyzing and
devouring tiny pests like you,
it works like a charm.
Little bummer!
What in the...
Didn't you hear a thing I said?
Your stand has got nothing on mine!
This bottle will be your
private arena, Narancia.
Hey, let me out of here, you ass!
Look, all its eyes are right on you.
Each of those eight peepers is
watching your every teeny-weeny move.
Bastard, I said let me out!
Damn it!
Oh yeah, don't assume that its bite will
send you to a swift and peaceful oblivion.
Its venom will first paralyze your
muscles, rendering your body immobile.
But it's what happens after the
paralysis that's really terrifying.
It'll grab you and inject both the venom
and the digestive enzyme
deep into your body.
The deadly cocktail of
enzymes will then slowly but
surely liquefy your insides
into a pulp of viscous slime.
Then slurpity slurp.
Keep in mind you'll be fully conscious,
meaning you'll be able to speak
as it's lunching on your flesh.
But word to the wise, friend, I strongly
urge you to spill the beans now.
Just tell me where you're
hiding that damn girl. I mean,
I really prefer not to have to watch a kid
become the liquid lunch
of some giant spider.
It's so fast!
Take this!
A glass shard?
Where the hell did he get that thing?
It's webbing!
But when did it...
There's the bite.
How about it?
Enjoying the convulsions
and paralysis yet?
Just hurry up and come clean.
This is your last chance
to save your heart.
Do you think I'd ever gave to you?
Eight Eyes is pumping you full
of digestive enzymes as we speak.
Now your organs will melt, huh?
What's that?
This paper.
You dropped it when you
took out that glass shard.
And all of a sudden, kid, I'm getting
real glad I decided to pick it up.
To think, everything I need might be
right here on this tiny piece of paper.
This here is a driving map of the city.
And not only that.
The damn thing's covered
in pencil markings.
Someone was trying not to get lost.
Could you be any dumber?
I just have to follow your little
path back to where you started from!
So this is where you're keeping the girl!
You came from a vineyard 20
kilometers to the southeast!
Crazy mille, Narancia!
Have fun being eaten alive!
See you when itsy Bites
spider here shits ya! Idiota!
20 kilometers to the southeast,
I'll find their boss's
daughter ripe for the picking!
I did it!
Feel free to keep your trap shut!
My little bomber's ability detects
and follows traces of carbon dioxide.
See, it's a colorless gas, and living
organisms aren't the only things that emit it.
The combustion of matter
also gives off the stuff.
Hey, I just remembered.
When I was chasing you earlier with Lil'
Bomber, I also happened to nail that car.
Oh yeah, I'm pretty sure I turned
that gas tank into Swiss cheese.
I can't tell exactly where those
bullet holes are from here.
But even so, looking back,
I remember thinking those bullet holes
were blazing when my radar picked them up.
And the carbon dioxide made them
easy pickings for Lil' Bomber.
So I fired away you see I
wasn't actually shooting
at the spider back
there those bullet holes
were super tiny so it
took a little while for
things to get cooking I
was worried for a bit but
What?!
What shitty luck.
All of that stuff I
bought is getting torched.
Whatever will I do?!
Man,
it sure feels great to not have to worry
about giant-sized spider bites anymore.
How dare you?!
I'm gonna put your entire gang
of stones off of that, Katsune!
I'm gonna find your hideout!
You think your little vineyard is safe?
Think again!
I hope you've prepared yourself!
Naranja!
Tiny feet!
What?
Who the hell puts a fire out with
blood from their cut wrist? Shit! Shit!
What's my move?
I can't let him get away now!
I'll just have to find
him with Lil' Bomber!
Well, so much for that idea.
The radar can't find him!
Flames are in the way!
My lucky break.
Poor dumb Narancia.
Because you set the car on fire, the flames
are giving off too much carbon dioxide,
so you can't use your
radar to pin me down.
At this point, I guess it's
safe to say that I win.
I know where to find the boss's daughter
Now all I have to do is ditch this
shithole and tell my team then we're
gonna blow you and your teammates to hell
Assassinations are what we do best.
It's our specialty. See what?
I'll make sure we're square real soon.
You won't ever have to see me again.
I win
Since it's so hard to pinpoint
your nasty-ass breath?
You know, because of the
roaring fires blazing around us?
I think I'll just have to
feed those flames more!
Once I light up this street,
Baby's Widow Assassin's gonna be crispier
than the crust of a pizza margarita!
I'll be damned if you get
away from me, Formazio!
You are deranged.
Even by psycho standards, you
actually set the damn street on fire!
Are you insane?
Well, are you?
Finally showed yourself.
Now I don't have to burn
down the whole city.
The reason that I asked if you were
insane was because of your actions.
They're telling me to kill you and
strike your ass down where you stand.
Your little firefest gave me the
cover I needed to get closer.
In case you've forgotten,
at this distance, my stand is a hell
of a lot faster than yours. Maybe.
Bring it, Narancia.
Yeah.
Tiny Beats!
It really blows, huh?
It looks like your
little shopping excursion
wasn't as cut and dried
as you thought it'd be.
Hey, Naranja.
Well, things are going to get
a lot worse from here on out.
For all, you cojone.
Go shopping, they tell me.
The mission's a failure.
I lost everything.
All the money, all the March.
All that's left is a bunch of ashes.
Run it by me again, Narancia?
It all burned up, I
told you! No, not that!
The part about the enemy knowing
where we've been hiding But I
took care of him right after You
really think it's that simple?
Ujarati, we all need to get the hell out
of here, now How many times did I warn you?
You can be such an idiot!
We should be commending him, I mean he
took out one of our enemies after all
Honestly guys, what else could he
have really done in that situation?
And now that the Hitman team has
figured out what we're up to,
a sensible boss would tell his team
how to get out of this awful mess.
Giorno!
I think we should all stay right here, at
least until we hear from the boss again.
Listen to the prodigy preach.
Didn't realize you were our advisor.
What if we don't hear from him?
Then all of us here would be
nothing but sitting ducks.
Wild guesses won't help us, kid!
Bucciarati!
I think we just got a
message from the boss.
The boss always sends his
directives to Kapos this way,
but this is the very first
one sent to Bucciarati.
I'll review the directive.
Proceed to Pompeii.
I have hidden a key somewhere
near the Cave Cana mosaic.
Investigate, Ragazzi.
This hidden key operates
the vehicle that will
allow you safe passage as
you deliver my daughter.
What kind of vehicle
would allow us to do that
it's a helicopter think
about it for a second.
It's so obvious with
a helicopter we can go
anywhere without being
followed Pompeii is about
15 kilometers away from
here we could get there
in an hour plenty of time
to find the key okay.
Okay, Fugo, Abacchio, Giorno, you three
will travel to Pompeii to secure that key.
Mr.
Narancia and I will remain here and
protect Trish from the Hitman team.
Retrieve the key.
Radio back when it's clear.
That's when the rest of us
will meet you with Trish.
From there, we'll be on our way.
Godspeed.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see!
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me!
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaky you is all I need.
I need your body.
Tonight, you got my time.
Tonight, you won't be sorry!
Tonight, you got my mind.
You got my mind, I don't
want to do it for you.
What must I say?
What must I do to show how
much I'm gonna freak you?
What must I say?
What must I do to show how
much I'm gonna freak you?
Thank you.